Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- D, 1865-2012; 3.5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Democratic National Committee: Election Campaign Handbook, 1956 (Box 116)
  - Democratic National Convention (New York, NY): Non Delegates Handbook, undated (Box 31)
  - Democratic Party of Vietnam: Cards, undated (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Federation (U.S.), 1957 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Federation: Greater Miami Branch, 1964 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (U.S.) I, 1970-1980 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (U.S.) II, 1970-1980 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (U.S.) III, 1970-1980 (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (U.S.) IV, 1970-1980, undated (Box 31)
  - Democratic Socialists at NYU, 1998- (Box 32)
  - Democratic Socialists of America I, 1981-2012 (Box 32, Box 124, Folder 3-5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America II, 1980s- (Box 32)
  - Democratic Socialists of America III, 1980s- (Box 32)
  - Democratic Socialists of America: Youth Sector, 1980s (Box 32)
  - Democratic Student Association, 1880-2015 (Box 32)
  - Demokratia (New York, NY), 1974, undated (Box 32)
  - Denver Chicano Liberation Defense Committee, 1973 (Box 32)
  - Descendants of the American Revolution, 1940, undated (Box 32)
  - Desis Rising Up and Moving (DRUM), 2001-2004, undated (Box 32)
  - Detroit Coalition to End the War Now, undated (Box 32)
  - Detroit Committee to Keep America out of the War [in Vietnam], undated (Box 32)
  - Detroit Free Press, 1970 (Box 32)
  - Detroit Labor College, 1933 (Box 32)
  - Detroit Labor Committee for Peace and Justice, undated (Box 32)
  - Detroit Working People's Association, 2005 (Box 32)
  - Deutsche-Anarcho Syndikalisten, 1936 (Box 32)
  - Deutschen Sozialdemokratischen Arbeiterpartei in Der Tschechoslowakischen Republik, 1922-1923 (Box 32)
  - Deutscher Freihiets-Bund (New York, NY), 1935 (Box 32)
  - Develop Don't Destroy (Brooklyn, NY), 2004 (Box 32)
  - Development Education Centre (Toronto, Canada), 1973-1975 (Box 32)
  - Development Group for Alternative Policies, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Dial Publishing Company (New York, NY), undated (Box 32)
  - Diggers Communications Company, circa 1967 (Box 32)
  - Dill Pickle Press (Muscatine, IA), circa 1970s (Box 32)
  - Direct Action for Justice in Palestine, 2002- (Box 32)
  - Direct Action Network, 1999- (Box 32)
  - Direct Action Network (Chicago, IL), 2002 (Box 32)
  - Direct Action Network (New York, NY), 2002 (Box 32)
  - Disarm Education Fund, undated (Box 32)
  - Disney/Haiti Justice Campaign, undated (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Dispossessed Network, 2000- (Box 32)
  - Dissent (New York, NY): Serial, 1961- (Box 32)
  - Distributive Worker, 1971 (Box 32)
  - Dollars and Sense (Somerville, MA), undated (Box 32)
  - Downtown Community School, undated (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Draft Law Group (Yale Law School), 1968 (Box 32)
  - Draft Resistance Committee (Detroit, MI), undated (Box 32)
  - Draft Resisters Union Movement, 1967 (Box 32)
  - Dramatic Society (New York, NY), 1937 (Box 32)
  - Drop the I-Word Campaign, undated (Box 32)
  - Drop the Rock (Rockefeller Drug Laws), 2001- (Box 32)
  - Drunken Boat (New York, NY), 1994- (Box 32)
  - Du Quoin Miners Defense Committee, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Dubois Theater Guild, undated (Box 32)
  - Duke Progressive Alliance (Duke University), 2002-2003 (Box 32)
  - DYKE Action Machine (DAM!), 2002- (Box 32)
  - Dykes Against Racism Everywhere, 1989- (Box 32)
  - Dykes for an American Revolution: Poetry, 1966, undated (Box 32)
- E, 1904-2019; 3.5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Earth First!, 2004 (Box 32)
  - Earth Liberation Front, undated (Box 32)
  - Earth Matters!, 2002- (Box 32)
  - East and West Association (U.S.), 1942 (Box 32)
  - East Bay Civil Rights Congress, undated (Box 32)
  - East Bay Women's Liberation, 1969 (Box 32)
  - East Coast Conference of Socialist Sociologists, 1974-1976 (Box 32)
  - East Coast Conspiracy to Save Lives, 1970 (Box 32)
  - EastRev, undated (Box 32)
  - East Side Federation of Italians to Defend America, undated (Box 32)
  - East Side Service Organization, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - East Side Tenants Moratorium Committee, undated (Box 32)
  - East Timor Action Network, 2011, undated (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperative League (Brooklyn, NY) I, 1938-1948 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperative League (Brooklyn, NY) II, 1938-1948 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperative Wholesale I, 1941-1942 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperative Wholesale II, 1940-1943 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Cooperatives (New York, NY), 1947 (Box 32)
  - Eastern Marxist Scholars' Conference (New York, NY), 1980 (Box 32)
  - Eastern New England Conference for Equal Opportunities, 1940-1944 (Box 32)
  - Eastern States' Socialist Conference, undated (Box 32)
  - Ecology Action East (New York, NY), 1969-1970 (Box 32)
  - Ecology Action Educational Institute (Berkeley, CA), 1960s (Box 32)
  - Economists Against the Arms Race (New York, NY), undated (Box 32)
  - Ediciones Españolas, 1936-1938 (Box 32)
  - Editions Servier le Peuple (Corona, Elmhurst, NY), 1983 (Box 32)
  - Editorial Argonauta (Buenos Aires, Argentina), 1920-1921 (Box 32)
  - Education Exploration Center, 1980 (Box 32)
  - Educational and Cultural Fund of the Electrical Industry, 1991 (Box 32)
  - Educational Policies Commission, 1944 (Box 32)
  - Eighth CD for Impeachment (Jerrold Nadler, New York), 2008- (Box 33)
  - El Comité-M.I.N.P., undated (Box 33)
  - El Grupo Escindido, 2012 (Box 33)
  - El Rescate Human Rights Department "Report of the Salvadora Trade Union Movement", 1985 (Box 33)
  - Electoral Reform Society, 1913 (Box 33)
  - Elmira Unemployment Council, 1935 (Box 33)
  - Embassies of Reconciliation (London, U.K.), 1937 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee I, 1954-1964, undated (Box 33)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee II, 1955-1964, undated (Box 33)
  - Emergency Coalition Against Martial Law, circa 1990s (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee for a National Mobilization Against Racism, 1974 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee for Peace in the Middle East and Vietnam, undated (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars, 1937-1941 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists, undated (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee on Rent and Housing, Inc. (New York, NY), undated (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee on United States Policy in Nicaragua, undated (Box 33)
  - Emergency Committee to Defend Democracy in Chile (San Jose, CA), undated (Box 33)
  - Emergency Conference Committee (U.S.), 1970, undated (Box 33)
  - Emergency National Council Against U.S. Intervention in Central America and the Caribbean, 1986 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Peace Campaign (U.S.), 1936 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Peace Mobilization Committee of Greater New York, 1940 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Project for Saigon Civilian Prisoners, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Emergency Public Integration Committee, undated (Box 33)
  - Emma Lazarus Federation of Jewish Women's Clubs, 1981-1983 (Box 33)
  - Emmaus House (New York, NY), undated (Box 33)
  - Empire State College: Center for Labor Studies, 1974-1977 (Box 33)
  - Empire State College: Faculty Action Committee, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Empire State College: Harry Van Arsdale Jr. School of Labor Studies, 1985- (Box 33)
  - Employees for Improved Mass Transit, undated (Box 33)
  - Employed and Unemployed Citizens of Colorado, undated (Box 33)
  - Employers' Association of Boston, 1904 (Box 33)
  - Employment Research Associates, 1980s (Box 33)
  - End Poverty League, 1934 (Box 33)
  - End the Draft Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 33)
  - End the Draft in '63, 1963 (Box 33)
  - English Land Restoration League, undated (Box 33)
  - English People's Convention, 1941 (Box 33)
  - Enraged Ones, circa 1972 (Box 33)
  - Enron, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Environment Group, Inc., 1970-1976 (Box 33)
  - Environmental Action Coalition, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Environmental Action Foundation (Washington, DC), undated (Box 33)
  - Environmental Project on Central America, 1989 (Box 33)
  - Environmentalists for Full Employment (Washington, DC), 1985 (Box 33)
  - Equal Income Party, 1934 (Box 33)
  - Equality League (New York, NY), undated (Box 33)
  - Ethical Anarchism (Tucson, AZ), undated (Box 33)
  - Ethical Culture School/ Fieldston School (New York, NY), 1934 (Box 33)
  - Ethical Humanist Society, undated (Box 33)
  - Ethiopian Revolution Information Center, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Ethiopian Students Union in North America, 1971-1976 (Box 33)
  - Étudier L'Anarchisme, 1999 (Box 33)
  - Eugene Debs School (New York, NY), undated (Box 33)
  - Eugene V. Debs Foundation I, 1995-2021 (Box 33, Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Eugene V. Debs Foundation II, 1995- (Box 33)
  - Eugene Dennis Defense Committee, undated (Box 33)
  - Evangelicals for Social Action, 1983 (Box 33)
  - Every Mother is a Working Mother Network, 2002, undated (Box 33)
  - Everyday Apocalypse, undated (Box 33)
  - Ex-Service Movement for Peace (Great Britain), 1951-1953 (Box 33)
  - External Tendency of the 1st, 1983 (Box 33)
  - Extinction Rebellion: Demonstration in Bobst Library, 2019 (Box 121)
  - Eye Opener, undated (Box 33)
- F, 1900-2008; 11 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 4 oversize shared boxes
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain), 1913-2000 (Box 33)
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain): Pamphlets, 1900 (Box 33)
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain): Pamphlets I, 1906-1990 (Box 33)
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain): Pamphlets II, 1906-1990 (Box 33)
  - Fabian Society (Great Britain): Pamphlets III, 1906-1990 (Box 33)
  - Facing Reality Publishing Committee, 1964 (Box 33)
  - Facing Reality Publications, Friends Of (Detroit, MI), 1970 (Box 33)
  - Fact: A Monograph a Month (London, U.K), 1937 (Box 33)
  - Faculty Action, undated (Box 33)
  - Faculty of Social Science (New York, NY), 1958 (Box 33)
  - Fair Play for Cuba Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 34)
  - Fair Play for Cuba Committee: Pamphlets, 1961-1964 (Box 34)
  - Fair Share for Working Families, undated (Box 34)
  - Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting, 2000, undated (Box 34)
  - Falling Wall Press, 1971-1975 (Box 34)
  - Families of Resisters of Amnesty, 1973 (Box 34)
  - Families of the Baltimore Smith Act Victims, 1951 (Box 34)
  - Families United for Racial and Economic Equality (FUREE) (Brooklyn, NY), undated (Box 34)
  - Family and Friends of Daniel McGowan, undated (Box 34)
  - Family Trust (New York, NY), 1970 (Box 34)
  - Fannie Lou Hamer Project, 2000-2001, undated (Box 34)
  - FanTasia Festival, 2000 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Far East Reporter, 1959 (Box 34)
  - Far East Spotlight, undated (Box 34)
  - Farm Credit Administration, 1937-1959 (Box 34)
  - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Association of Minnesota, 1925, 1936 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party, 1920-1924 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party, 1932-1936 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party (Cook County, IL), undated (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party of Wayne County (Mich.), undated (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party (New Hampshire), undated (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party (New York), 1929 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Party (Washington), 1923 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Political Federation, undated (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Progressive Federation, 1920-1935 (Box 34)
  - Farmer-Labor Reconstruction League of Oklahoma, circa 1920s (Box 34)
  - Farmers National Committee for Action, undated (Box 34)
  - Farmers' Union Co-operative Hospital Association, undated (Box 34)
  - Farmworker Justice Fund (Washington, DC), 2001- (Box 34)
  - Federación Anarquista Internacional (Chile), 1960 (Box 34)
  - Federación Ibérica de Juventudes Libertarias, undated (Box 34)
  - Federación Obrera Regional Argentina, 1961 (Box 34)
  - Federación Universitaria a Socialista Puertorriqueño, 1974 (Box 34)
  - Federal Art Project, 1934-1938 (Box 34)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America I, 1918-1946, undated (Box 34)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America II, 1918-1946, undated (Box 34)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Administration: Workers Education, 1934-1935 (Box 34)
  - Federal Ministry for Expellees, Refugees, and War Victims, 1959 (Box 34)
  - Federated Americans Against Israeli Racism (FAIR), undated (Box 34)
  - Federated Associations for Impartial Review, undated (Box 34)
  - Federated Farmer-Labor Party (U.S.), undated (Box 34)
  - Federated Industries of Washington, 1924-1925 (Box 34)
  - Federated Labor Schools of Western Pennsylvania: Flier, undated (Box 34)
  - Federated Press: Eastern Bureau, 1943- (Box 34)
  - Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal (FIRR), 1992-1994 (Box 34)
  - Federation for Progress, 1984 (Box 34)
  - Federation for Support of Jewish Philanthropic Societies, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Consumers (New York, NY), 1917 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Labour Conference, 1959 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Residential Settlements (Great Britain), 1922 (Box 34)
  - Federation of the Russian Anarchist-Communist Group of U.S.A. and Canada, 1934 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Unemployed Workers' League of America, undated (Box 34)
  - Fellowship Farm Co-Operative Association (Stelton, NJ), 1912 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship House, 1913-1917 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.) I, 1970- (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.) II, 1970- (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.) III, 1970- (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.) IV, 1970- (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (U.S.): Local Volunteers Program, Aids for Peace Action, 1957- (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Socialist Christians, 1938 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Southern Churchmen, 1946 (Box 34)
  - Fellowship of Youth for Peace, undated (Box 34)
  - Female Labor Reform Association, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Female Liberation/Cell 16 (Boston, MA), 1969-1970 (Box 35)
  - Female Liberation of Nashville, TN, 1969 (Box 35)
  - Feminist Art Journal, undated (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Feminist Book Mart, undated (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Feminist Center for Human Growth and Development, Inc., undated (Box 35)
  - Feminist Majority Foundation, undated (Box 35)
  - Feminist Organization for Communication, Action and Service, 1968 (Box 35)
  - Feminist Press, 1972-1985 (Box 35)
  - Feminist Union of New Haven (Connecticut), undated (Box 35)
  - Feminists (New York, NY), 1969 (Box 35)
  - Feminists of Children's Media, 1971-1972 (Box 35)
  - Fernwood Press (Toronto, Canada), 2001- (Box 35)
  - Ferrer Colony (Stelton, N.J.), 1936 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Festival Del Pueblo (Boston, MA), undated (Box 35)
  - Fierce! (Fabulous Independent Educated for Community Empowerment), 2002- (Box 35)
  - Fifteenth Street Manifesto Group, 2008 (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee I, undated (Box 35)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee II, undated (Box 35)
  - Fight Back, 1979 (Box 35)
  - Fight Back Teach-in, 2011 (Box 35)
  - Fight for Immigrants Everywhere (F.I.R.E.), 2018 (Box 124, Folder 15, Box Shared Tamiment 184, Folder 14)
  - Fight Imperialism Stand Together (FIST), 2007, undated (Box 35)
  - Fighting Worker (Chicago, IL), 1944 (Box 35)
  - Film and Photo League, undated (Box 35)
  - Film Industry for Peace, 1970 (Box 35)
  - Films for Democracy, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Financial Reform Association (Liverpool, U.K.), undated (Box 35)
  - Fincher's Trades' Review: Newspaper, circa 1860s (Box 35)
  - Fire and Flames, undated (Box 35)
  - First American Conference on Democracy and Terms of Peace, 1917 (Box 35)
  - First Nations North and South, 1999- (Box 35)
  - First-Run Features, 1983 (Box 35)
  - First-Run Icarus Films, 1995- (Box 35)
  - Flatbush Committee to End the War in Vietnam, undated (Box 35)
  - Flight Back (New York, NY), 1979 (Box 35)
  - Florida East Coast Railway (St. Augustine, FL), 1965 (Box 35)
  - Florida Right to Work Committee (Tallahassee, FL), 1962 (Box 35)
  - Flower City Conspiracy, 1970 (Box 35, Box Shared Tamiment 184, Folder 15)
  - FOI Service Center -- Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Folkeuniversitetet I Kobenhavn, undated (Box 35)
  - Folksingers Guild, 1969 (Box 35)
  - Food First, 1988 (Box 35)
  - Food Not Bombs, 2009- (Box 35)
  - For the Scrapbook of Nancy and Ronald Reagan, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1968 (Box 35)
  - Foreign Language Information Service (U.S.), undated (Box 35)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1949 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1950 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1950 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1951 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1952 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1953 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1953 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1954 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1955 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1956 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1958 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1959 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1960 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1961 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1961 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1962 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1963 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1963 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1964 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1965 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1965 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) III, 1965 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1966 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1966 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1967 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1967 (Box 118)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1968 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1968 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1969 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1970 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1971 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1972 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1973 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1974 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) II, 1974 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China) I, 1975 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1976 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1977 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), 1978, 1984 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Press (China), undated (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic People's Republic of Korea), 1961-1965 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic People's Republic of Korea): U.S.S. Pueblo, 1968 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic People's Republic of Korea), 1970 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic People's Republic of Korea), 1972-1977 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1958 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1959 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam) I, 1960 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam) II, 1960 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1961 (Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1962 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam) I, 1963 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam) II, 1963 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam) I, 1964 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam) II, 1964 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam) I, 1965 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam) II, 1965 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1966 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1967 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1968 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1969 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1970 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Democratic Republic of Vietnam), 1975-1979 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1939 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1942 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1943 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1944 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1946 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1947 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1948 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1949 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union) I, 1950 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union) II, 1950 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union) I, 1951 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union) II, 1951 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union) I, 1952 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union) II, 1952 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1953 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1954 (Box 121)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1955 (Box 121)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1956 (Box 121)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1957 (Box 121)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), 1959-1963 (Box 121)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow, Soviet Union), undated (Box 121)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1966 (Box 35)
  - Foreign Policy Council of New York Democrats, 1966 (Box 35)
  - Forever in Struggle Together (FIST) People of Color Grassroots Organization, undated (Box 35)
  - Foro Mundial del Saber Aplicado, 2008 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Fort Hood Three Defense Committee, 1966 (Box 35)
  - Forum Pamphlets, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Foundation for Change (New York, NY), undated (Box 35)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Inc., 1972 (Box 35)
  - Foundation for Independent Video and Film (New York, NY), 1983-1984 (Box 35)
  - Foundation for International Social Hygiene, 1979 (Box 35)
  - Foundation for Religious Action in the Social and Civil Order (FRASCO), undated (Box 35)
  - Foundation for the Study of Independent Social Ideas, 1989- (Box 35)
  - Four Arrows (York, PA), undated (Box 35)
  - Four Continent Book Corporation: Catalog, 1962 (Box 35)
  - Fourth Army for Self Defense, 1969 (Box 35)
  - Fourth International I, 1943-1969 (Box 35, Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Fourth International II, 1943- (Box 35)
  - Fourth Internationalist Tendency, 1981-1984 (Box 35)
  - Fourth Internationalist Tendency I, 1985-1989 (Box 35)
  - Fourth Internationalist Tendency II, 1985-1989 (Box 35)
  - Fourth Internationalist Tendency I, 1990- (Box 35)
  - Fourth Internationalist Tendency II, 1990- (Box 35)